

# **Hudson Kennedy**

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

#### CONTACT

Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ hudsonkennedyjr/

Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ \_hudson.9kj/



# **ABOUT ME**

I had contact with the technology area about 10 years ago, working with VB.net and HTML, during the journey I took some courses, where in 2018 I started my Technologist in management processes and in return I went back to the technology area, to work with Javascript, specifically in Frontend, where I have studied and taken several courses, graduated in Process Management, with an emphasis on Process Management and Optimization, and I always wanted to acquire more knowledge and evolve professionally. In 2021 I started my MBA in Software Engineering, where I learned many new things and continue to evolve every day. I will continue to improve myself daily as a Fullstack Developer and Software Engineer, seeking to acquire more experience and knowledge!



# **EXPERIENCE**

### **Fullstack Developer**

August 2022 - at moment

#### **Full Technical Consultant**

January 2022 - April 2022

# E-commerce Analyst / Front-end Developer

February 2019 - June 2021

#### Freelancers/Personal Works

February 2018 - at moment

## **Cast Group**

Working directly with the Bosch customer, in the directives and maintenance/refactoring negotiations code using Angular and Typescript.

# **VILT Brazil Information Systems**

Fullstack Consulting, working with Java in Backend and Angular/React in Frontend, using Platform programs Adobe Experience Manager(AEM), providing services for several clients such as Porto, CVC and etc.

# **DT3 Group**

Invoice issuance, marketplaces, website development in React.JS, image optimization and responsible for ERP Bling integration.

# Appen Projects/99Freelas/Capitona Rio

I did some freelance work with Shopify, using Angular Js, Angular 7+, Vanilla Js, Jquery, Bootstrap and Sass.



# **ACADEMIC EDUCATION**

# **Harvard University**

2023

# Post Graduate

Science Computer

# **Single College of MG**

2021 - 2022

# MBA

Software Engineering

## Estácio de Sá College

2018 - 2020

#### **Technologist**

Management processes



Hudson Kennedy

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

UI/UX DESIGNER

#### CONTACT

Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ hudsonkennedyjr/

Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ \_hudson.9kj/



# HTML/CSS/Jquery/Javascript/Angular/React/VueJs/NodeJs Git/Github/NPM/YARN/Wordpress/Shopify/Bling

5 Years of Experience

**APIs** 

4 Years of Experience

Bootstrap/Typescript/UI-UXDesinger/Figma/Photoshop

3 Years of Experience

Less/Sass/TailwindCss

1 Year of Experience

JAVA/PHP/Laravel/Docker/Webpack

6 Months of Experience



## **EXTRACURRICULAR COURSES**

DIO - Components, Methods and Lifecycle with Vue.js - 2022

DIO - Component Properties and Directives with Vue.js - 2022

DIO - Bootcamp Eduzz - Fullstack Developer - 2022

DIO - Working with SPA Pages with Angular - 2022

DIO - Working with Components in React - 2022

DIO - Component architecture and front-end complexity - 2022

Adobe Professional – AEM Sites Business Practitioner - 2022

Adobe Professional – AEM Front-End Developer - 2022

Let's Code Course (Santander) - Dev Fullstack - 2021

MERN Stack Course (MongoDB, Express, React & NodeJS -

FaculdadeIV2 - 2021

Initial Vuejs Course - Vuejs Brazil - 2021

Basic to Advanced Javascript & Typescript Course (HTML/CSS/

NodeJs/React/MySQL/PostgreSQL/MariaDB/ - Udemy - 2020



#### **LANGUAGES**

Spanish - Basic

French - Basic

Italian - Basic

**English - Advanced** 



#### ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

Excel/Word /Power Point
Teams/Outlook/Skype
Wordpress/Shopify/ERP Bling
System Configurations
Windows
Computer Domain
Typing
Document Archiving
Internet in general
Google Chrome/Mozilla/Opera